Dave says I found that guys who are more
prone to side effects on trt overweight
alcohol consumption Etc receive less
side effects when starting trt compared
to injections have you seen this oh does
he mean cream when starting cream yes I
I totally agree totally agree and I I I
speculate that again same reason a lot
of guys get acne uh same reason for the
hemoglobin himatic issues you're
injecting foreign material you're
injecting seed oils you're injecting
conservatives into the body if you're
already a more fragile person
metabolically speaking or healthy uh
Health speaking I think the ability to
process those that stuff goes down uh
and so you can't just truly be focused
on the one variable you need to be on
which is the testosterone and how is it
affecting you I had this conversation
with a guy yesterday almost identical
and he's young and healthy so he's going
to reap the most rewards from starting
trt because he's already optimizing
everything in his life whereas you know
if I had a guy come to me that's 300 PBS
overweight massive belly uh drinks all
the time type two diabetic starting
testosterone those guys often makes them
just feel like crap I mean really not
all of them I mean I'll be I'll be
honest I've been surprised sometimes how
you know they do feel better um but it
depends on the person but yes in general
starting those guys on injections I just
tend to see more negatives um the one
thing with cream I noticed in my
overweight guys is about the first two
to four weeks they get uh increased
water water retention little edema in
their ankles and feet and they freak out
and always tell them it'll go away after
your body you know stabilizes and it
does I tell them you write it out
another couple weeks let me know if it
doesn't obviously um but almost every
case it goes back it goes away and same
thing with blood pressure spikes and
things like that but again they're
overweight they need to work on all that
stuff and that's why guys in the group
will ask these
questions about their hormones and
they're obviously not optimizing all the
other parts of their life yet so it's
like you can't you don't even need to be
talking about what your testosterone you
can't prove it one way or the other if
you're not already optimizing these
other variables because now you're
dealing with multiple things at once and
so it's hard to say so but anyway yeah I
agree Dave uh cream seems to have less
negatives when starting